Artur Rodzinski Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Correspondence, 1931-1976, bulk 1938-1953 (Box 1-11)
  - Małcużyński, Witold, 1943 (Box 6/33)
  - Malinverni, Carlo see Agenzia Lirica Concertistica Internazionale
  - Maliszewski, W., 1934 (Box 6/34)
  - Malko, Nicolai, 1945 (Box 6/35)
  - Mamorsky, Eleanor Lodge, 1943 (Box 6/36)
  - Mamorsky, Morris see National Broadcasting Company, Inc.
  - Manley, Michael F. see Equitable Life Assurance Society of the United States
  - Mapleson, Alfred J., 1952 (Box 6/37)
  - Marian, Epstein, 1942 (Box 6/38)
  - Marionette Productions, 1951 (Box 6/39)
  - Marre, Lotte see Frank S. Hartley Jewels
  - Mártay, Béla, 1942 (Box 6/40)
  - Martina, Sister M., 1942 (Box 6/41)
  - Mason, Daniel Gregory, 1945 (Box 6/42)
  - Massachusetts. Dept. of Corporations and Taxation, 1942 (Box 6/43)
  - Massachusetts Indemnity Insurance Company, 1950 (Box 6/44)
  - Masterpieces of the 20th century see Nabokov, Nicolas
  - Mathieu, André see Pelletier, Wilfrid
  - Matzenauer, Margarete, 1945 (Box 6/45)
  - Mauder, Jack G. see General Motors Corporation. Cadillac Motor Car Division
  - Maxwell, J. G., 1942 (Box 6/46)
  - May, Frank G., 1945 (Box 6/47)
  - Mayfield & Mayfield, 1952 (Box 6/48)
  - Mayfield, Earle B. Jr. see Mayfield & Mayfield
  - Maynor, Dorothy, n.d. (Box 6/49)
  - MCA see Music Corporation of America
  - McArthur, Edwin, 1943-1947 (Box 6/50)
  - McBride, Robert, 1942 (Box 6/51)
  - McCann, Mary N. see New Orleans Symphony Society
  - McCullagh, E. Perry, 1942 (Box 6/52)
  - McDonald, Harl, 1942-1945 (Box 6/53)
  - McGinnis, Robert, 1942 (Box 6/54)
  - McKay, George Frederick, 1945 (Box 6/55)
  - Meilink & Company, Inc., n.d. (Box 6/56)
  - Mena, Luis E., 1939 (Box 6/57)
  - Menuhin, Yehudi, 1943 (Box 6/58)
  - Merchandise Mart (Chicago, Ill.), 1948 (Box 6/59)
  - Mercury Music Corporation, 1943 (Box 6/60)
  - Mero-Irion, Yolanda, 1942 (Box 6/61)
  - Merrill L. Thomas Real Estate Insurance, 1948-1951 (Box 6/62)
  - Mertens, André see Columbia Concerts Corporation (Columbia Broadcasting System) see Haensel & Jones see Mertens, Parmelee & Brown, Inc.
  - Mertens, Parmelee & Brown, Inc., 1949 (Box 6/63)
  - Metropolitan Musical Bureau, 1946 (Box 6/64)
  - Metropolitan Opera (New York, N.Y.), 1951 (Box 6/65)
  - Meyer, Abe see Music Corporation of America
  - Michal, Grunspan, 1942 (Box 6/66)
  - Milbank, Tweed, Hope & Hadley, 1949 (Box 6/67)
  - Milhaud, Darius, 1945 (Box 6/68)
  - Miller, Charles, 1942-1945 (Box 6/69)
  - Miller, Charles, 1943 (Box 6/70)
  - Millett, O.E., 1944 (Box 6/71)
  - Mills Music, Inc., 1942-1945 (Box 6/72)
  - Milwaukee County (Wis.). Park Commission, 1950-1951 (Box 6/73)
  - Miness, Irwin, 1951 see also Jaffe & Stern (Box 6/74)
  - Ministero delle Poste e delle Telecommunicazioni, 1952 (Box 6/75)
  - Mischakoff, Mischa, 1942 (Box 6/76)
  - Mitchell, Raymond Earle, 1943-1950 (Box 6/77)
  - Moe, Henry Allen see John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation
  - Mohaupt, Richard, 1942-1943 (Box 6/78)
  - Monath, Hortense, 1944 (Box 6/79)
  - Monroe, Harry L., 1948 (Box 6/80)
  - Montagu’s and Cox & Cardale, 1951 (Box 6/81)
  - Monteux, Doris Gerald see Monroe, Harry L.
  - Mooney, Hahn, Loeser, Keough & Freedheim, 1942 (Box 6/82)
  - Moore-McCormack Lines, Inc., 1949 (Box 6/83)
  - Moreland, Helen Hall, 1949 (Box 6/84)
  - Morgan, D.P., n.d. (Box 6/85)
  - Morgenthau, Mrs. Henry Jr. see Soviet Union. Posol’stvo (U.S.)
  - Morini, Erica, 1946 (Box 6/86)
  - Moritz, Edvard, 1942-1943 (Box 6/87)
  - Moross, Jerome, 1942 (Box 6/88)
  - Morris, Harold, 1942-1947 (Box 6/89)
  - Morris, Newbold see Violin Teachers Guild
  - Morris, Suzy, 1950 (Box 6/90)
  - Morris, Willavene S. see Music Guild
  - Morse, Richard, 1945 (Box 6/91)
  - Moscow State Philharmonic Orchestra see Moskovskaia gosudarstvennaia filarmoniia. Simfonicheskiĩ orkestr
  - Moskovskaia gosudarstvennaia filarmoniia. Simfonicheskiĩ orkestr, 1935 (Box 6/92)
  - Motion Picture Producers and Distributors of America, 1940 (Box 6/93)
  - Moye, L. see Professional Insurance Company
  - Muenzer, Hans, 1942 (Box 6/94)
  - Munch, Charles see Boston Symphony Orchestra
  - Mungo, F. see Automobile club d’italia
  - Municipal Chorus of San Francisco, 1950 (Box 6/95)
  - Municipal Electric Plant, 1953 (Box 6/96)
  - Municipalidad de la Ciudad de Buenos Aires see Teatro Colón (Buenos Aires, Argentina)
  - Muriel Francis, 1951 (Box 6/97)
  - Murray, J. Ralph, 1949 (Box 6/98)
  - Music Academy of the West, 1950 (Box 6/99)
  - Music Corporation of America, 1949-1950 (Box 6/100)
  - Music Daniel see Sociedad Musical Daniel
  - Music Guild, 1942 (Box 6/101)
  - Music Research Foundation, Inc., n.d. (Box 6/102)
  - Music Teachers’ Quarterly, n.d. (Box 6/103)
  - Musical America, 1944 (Box 6/104)
  - Musical Arts Association (Cleveland, Ohio), 1939 (Box 6/105)
  - Musical Courier, 1950-1951 (Box 6/106)
  - Mutch, J.E. see National Symphony Orchestra Association (Washington, D.C.)
  - Muto, Mrs. Irene see Motion Picture Producers and Distributors of America
  - Myers, Richard, 1945 (Box 6/107)
  - Mycielski, Zygmunt, 1950 (Box 6/108)
  - M miscellaneous, 1939-1945 (Box 7/1, 13/4)
  - Nabokov, Nicolas, 1941-1952 (Box 7/2, 60/4)
  - Napiwocki, Edward, 1942 (Box 7/3)
  - Napiwocki, Janina see Napiwocki, Edward
  - Nathan, Flora, 1945 (Box 7/4)
  - National Arts Foundation see Smith, Carleton
  - National Association for American Composers and Conductors see Spaeth, Sigmund Gottfried
  - National Broadcasting Company, Inc., 1942-1945 (Box 7/5)
  - National City Bank of New York, 1949 (Box 7/6)
  - National Concert and Artists Corporation, 1942-1950 see also Maier, Guy (Box 7/7)
  - National Concert and Artists Corporation, 1951-1953 see also Maier, Guy (Box 7/8)
  - National Federation of Music Clubs, 1945 see also Spaeth, Sigmund Gottfried (Box 7/9)
  - National Orchestral Association (U.S.), 1944-1945 (Box 7/10)
  - National Symphony Orchestra Association (Washington, D.C.), 1938-48 (Box 7/11)
  - NBC see National Broadcasting Company, Inc.
  - Nederlandsche Concertdirectie, 1952-1953 (Box 7/12)
  - New Orleans Symphony Society, 1951 (Box 7/13)
  - New York (City). Dept. of Finance, 1951 (Box 7/14)
  - New York Committee of the National War Fund, 1944 (Box 7/15)
  - New York Hospital. Society, 1949 (Box 7/16)
  - New York (N.Y.) Municipal Broadcasting System, 1945 (Box 7/17)
  - New York Orchestral Society Inc., 1965 (Box 7/18)
  - New York Philharmonic, 1943-1946 (Box 7/19)
  - New York Post, 1947 (Box 7/20)
  - New York Telephone Company see Mayfield & Mayfield
  - New York Times, 1949 see also Downes, Olin (Box 7/21)
  - NHK see Nihon Hōsō Kyōkai
  - Nichols, William Ichabod, 1905- see Muriel Francis
  - Nies-Berger, Edouard, 1942-1947 (Box 7/22)
  - Nihon Hōsō Kyōkai, 1952-1953 (Box 7/23)
  - Noelte, A. Albert, 1942 (Box 7/24)
  - Noma see Beu
  - Norden, Norris Lindsay, 1943 (Box 7/25)
  - North Elba (N.Y.: Town), 1949 (Box 7/26)
  - Northcutt, John Orlando see Hollywood Bowl Association
  - Northland Motors, 1952 (Box 7/27)
  - Novaes, Guiomar, 1947 (Box 7/28)
  - Novik, Morris S. see New York (N.Y.) Municipal Broadcasting System
  - Novotná, Jarmila see Music Research Foundation, Inc.
  - N miscellaneous, 1942-1954 (Box 7/29)
  - Oakes, J. Thomas, 1947 (Box 7/30)
  - Odnoposoff, Adolfo, 1950-1951 (Box 7/31)
  - Office Artistique Continental, 1949-1953 (Box 7/32)
  - Okun, Maxwell see Jaffe & Stern
  - Oldani, Luigi, 1952-1953 (Box 7/33)
  - Orchestral Association (Chicago, Ill.), 1948-1949 (Box 7/34)
  - Orchestre Symphonique de Montréal see Concerts Symphoniques de Montréal
  - Organización de conciertos gérard, 1950 (Box 7/35)
  - Organizzazione Internazionale Concerti see Finzi, Ada
  - Osham, Mr., 1949 (Box 7/36)
  - Ostroff, Irving, 1951 (Box 7/37)
  - Ovanin, Nikola Leonard, 1968 (Box 7/38)
  - Owens, Blanche A. see Cadman Choral Club of Santa Ana, Calif.
  - Oxford University Press, 1949 (Box 7/39)
  - O miscellaneous, 1942 (Box 7/40)
  - PAA see Pan American World Airways, Inc.
  - Paderewski, Ignace Jan, 1934 (Box 7/41)
  - Painchaud, P. T. see Liberty Mutual Insurance Company
  - Palester, Roman, 1947-1952 (Box 7/42)
  - Pan American World Airways, Inc., 1949 (Box 7/43)
  - Parents’ Institute (New York, N.Y.) see Muriel Francis
  - Parker, Caroline Bird see Town Hall Club
  - Parkinson, John, 1949 (Box 7/44)
  - Parks, Robert O., 1944-1945 (Box 7/45)
  - Parmelee, Horace J. see Columbia Concerts Corporation (Columbia Broadcasting System) see Haensel & Jones
  - Parmenter, Ross see New York Times
  - Pash, Donald A., 1945 (Box 7/46)
  - Passagila, 1951 (Box 7/47)
  - Pateras Pescara, Aurelio see Pescara, Aurelio
  - Pateras Pescara, Regina see Pescara, Aurelio
  - Patronato Pro-Música Sinfónica, 1949-1950 (Box 7/48)
  - Patt, Benjamin C. see Albert B. Ashforth, Inc.
  - Paul Small Artists Ltd., Inc., n.d. (Box 7/49)
  - Pechter, Israel E., 1951 (Box 7/50)
  - Peebles, Leighton H. see War Production Board
  - Pellegrini, Giovanni, 1951, Two photographs: 1) Pellegrini 2) Nuovo timpani. (Box 7/51)
  - Pelletier, Wilfrid, 1943 (Box 7/52)
  - Pennario, Leonard, 1944-1946 (Box 7/53)
  - Perc [Percival, Arthur] see [Powers], Dorotha
  - Perkins, Luke L. see Lake Placid Plumbing & Heating Co.
  - Pescara, Aurelio, 1943-1945 (Box 7/54)
  - Pettis, Ashley, 1935 (Box 7/55)
  - Peyton, Ann M. see United States. Foreign Service
  - Phillips, Burrill, 1943 (Box 7/56)
  - Pilecki, Leon, n.d. (Box 7/57)
  - Pimsleur, Solomon, 1943 (Box 7/58)
  - Piovesan, Alessandro see Biennale di Venezia
  - Piscator, Erwin, 1950 (Box 7/59)
  - Pittsburgh Symphony Society, 1949 (Box 7/60)
  - Poland. Ambasada (USSR), 1942 (Box 7/61)
  - Poleri, David, 1953 (Box 7/62)
  - Polesny, Eleanore see Polesny, Franz
  - Polesny, Ellis see Polesny, Franz
  - Polesny, Franz, 1949-1951 (Box 7/63)
  - Polish Arts Club, 1942 (Box 7/64)
  - Polish Embassy in USSR see Poland. Ambasada (USSR)
  - Pollard, Fred Jr. see General Electric X-Ray Corporation
  - Polmission see Poland. Ambasada (USSR)
  - Popov, Gavriil Nikolaevich, 1934 (Box 7/65)
  - Porges, Frank T. see Columbia Records, Inc.
  - Porrino, Ennio, 1952-1953 (Box 7/66)
  - Porter, Emily, 1942 (Box 7/67)
  - Porter, Kenneth see Isham & Isham
  - Portis, Robert B., 1950 (Box 7/68)
  - Powell, John, 1945 (Box 7/69)
  - [Powers], Dorotha, 1949 (Box 7/70)
  - Prawy, Marcel, 1951 (Box 7/71)
  - Preves, Milton see Gingold, Josef
  - Preves, Rebecca see Gingold, Josef
  - Price, Florence, 1942-1943 (Box 7/72)
  - Prime, E. Gardner see Isham & Isham
  - Primrose, William, 1943 (Box 7/73)
  - Professional Insurance Company, 1949-1950 (Box 7/74)
  - Proskauer, Rose, Goetz & Mendelsohn, 1952 (Box 7/75)
  - Prouty, A.W. see M. Steinert & Sons
  - Pulaski Day Memorial Committee, 1949 (Box 7/76)
  - Puletz, Rudy, 1944 (Box 7/77)
  - Quesada, Alfonso de see Sociedad Musical Daniel
  - Quesada, Ernesto de see Carvalho, Eleazar de see Sociedad Musical Daniel
  - Quesada, Ernesto de, Jr. see Sociedad Musical Daniel
  - Quick see Cowles Magazines, Inc.
  - Quimby, Arthur W. see Cleveland Orchestra
  - Quinn, Alfred, Price, 1942 (Box 7/78)
  - R.A.I. see Radio audizioni Italia
  - Rabin, George, n.d. (Box 7/79)
  - Radamsky, Marie see Radamsky, Sergei
  - Radamsky, Sergei, 1934-1935 see also Fitelson and Mayers see also Vosburgh, Carl J. (Box 8/1)
  - Radio audizioni Italia, 1948-1957 (Box 8/2)
  - Radio Corporation of America. RCA Victor Division, 1949 (Box 8/3)
  - Radio Italiana see Radio audizioni Italia
  - Radiotelevisione italiana see Radio audizioni Italia
  - Rapée, Erno, 1936 (Box 8/4)
  - Rathaus, Karol, 1939-1951 (Box 8/5)
  - Rathaus, Rudolf see Witkowski, Franiszek
  - Rathner, Norma, 1950 (Box 8/6)
  - Rauch, Greta, 1950 see also Columbia Records, Inc. (Box 8/7)
  - Ravinia Festival Association, 1942 (Box 8/8)
  - Razzi, Giulio see Radio audizioni Italia
  - Read, Gardner, 1942-1945 (Box 8/9)
  - Regules, Marisa, 1950 (Box 8/10)
  - Reifsmann, Oscar, 1949 (Box 8/11)
  - Reiner, Fritz, 1949 (Box 8/12)
  - Reiner, Gabriel see Cosmos Travel Bureau, Inc.
  - Reinheimer, Howard E. see Law offices Howard E. Reinheimer
  - Reisenberg, Nadia, 1941 (Box 8/13)
  - Reisman, Alexander, 1942 (Box 8/14)
  - Reiss, Egon, 1949-1950 (Box 8/15)
  - Reiter, Max, 1938-1939 (Box 8/16)
  - Remington Records, Inc. see Jaffe & Stern see Miness, Irwin
  - Rensselaer Cox, Sylvia van see Cox, Sylvia van Rensselaer
  - Research Program on the U.S.S.R. see Slusser, Robert M.
  - Reyes, Angel, 1950 (Box 8/17)
  - Ricci, Lisena see Luchini, F.
  - Richards, Mrs. Lisle C., 1944 (Box 8/18)
  - Richter-Tomsa, Elsa R., 1950 (Box 8/19)
  - Rickman, Edwin, T. see Municipal Chorus of San Francisco
  - Ricordi Americana, 1950 (Box 8/20)
  - Riegger Wallingford, 1942 (Box 8/21)
  - Ringbuchandlung, 1937 (Box 8/22)
  - Ringwall, Rudolph, 1942 (Box 8/23)
  - Riviera Beach (Fla.), 1949 (Box 8/24)
  - Rizzo, Francis A. see Steinway & Sons
  - Robbins, Cynthia see Muriel Francis
  - Robertson, Mrs. Ola, 1944 (Box 8/25)
  - Robeson, Paul, n.d. (Box 8/26)
  - Robin, J. see Vsesoiuznoe obshchestvo kul’turnoĭ sviazi s zagranitseĭ (Soviet Union)
  - Robison, Vivian Gilpin, 1944 (Box 8/27)
  - Robofsky, Abrasha, 1945 (Box 8/28)
  - Rochester Civic Music Association, 1947 (Box 8/29)
  - Rockefeller, Blanchette Hooker, 1951 (Box 8/30)
  - Rockefeller, Mrs. John D. Jr. see Rockefeller, Blanchette Hooker
  - Rockmore, Clara, 1945 (Box 8/31)
  - Rockmore, Robert see Barron, Rick & Rockmore
  - Roder, Milan, 1943 (Box 8/32)
  - Rodzinska, Jadwiga, 1940-1950 (Box 8/33)
  - Rodzinski, Artur, 1953 (Box 8/34)
  - Rodzinski, Halina, 1949-1951 see also Sociedad Musical Daniel (Box 8/35)
  - [Rodzinski], Ilse, 1951 (Box 8/36)
  - [Rodzinski], Witold, 1949-1952 (Box 8/37)
  - Rogers, Bernard, 1940-1948 (Box 8/38)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1946 (Box 8/39)
  - Rose, Alfred L. see Proskauer, Rose, Goetz & Mendelsohn
  - Rose, Leonard, 1943-1947 see also Gingold, Josef (Box 8/40)
  - Rosen, Leo see Greenbaum, Wolff & Ernst
  - Rosenberg, Robert, 1944 (Box 8/41)
  - Rosenthal, Manuel, 1946-1947 (Box 8/42)
  - Rosenwald, Hans see Chicago Musical College
  - Ross, Hugh, 1950 (Box 8/43)
  - Rot-Weiss-Rot, 1952 (Box 8/44)
  - Roth, Feri, 1944-1945 (Box 8/45)
  - Rothe, Friede F., 1945 (Box 8/46)
  - Rothfarb, Harry, 1944 (Box 8/47)
  - Roxas, Emilio Amico, 1942 (Box 8/48)
  - Royal Philharmonic Orchestra, 1958 (Box 8/49)
  - Rozenberg, J., 1949 (Box 8/50)
  - Rubinoff Enterprises, 1944 (Box 8/51, 60/5)
  - Rubinoff, Philip see Rubinoff Enterprises
  - Rubinstein, Beryl, 1933-1935 (Box 8/52)
  - Ruddock, Albert B. see Hollywood Bowl Association
  - Rudolph Wurlitzer Company, 1945 (Box 8/53)
  - Ruff, Margaret Carson see Metropolitan Opera (New York, N.Y.)
  - Rupp, Franz, 1944 (Box 8/54)
  - Russian War Relief, Inc., 1942 (Box 8/55)
  - Russian War Relief, Inc. Massachusetts Committee see Russian War Relief, Inc.
  - Rychlik, C.V., 1942 (Box 8/56)
  - Rychtarik, Richard, 1952 (Box 8/57)
  - Ryerson, Edward L. (Edward Larned), n.d. (Box 8/58)
  - R miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 8/59)
  - Sabatini, Guglielmo, 1943 (Box 8/60)
  - Sadlier, John D., 1944 (Box 8/61)
  - Salzedo, Carlos, 1935 (Box 8/62)
  - Sam Goody, 1959 (Box 8/63)
  - Samaroff Stokowski, Olga see Columbia Concerts Corporation (Columbia Broadcasting System)
  - Saminsky, Lazare, 1935-1946 (Box 8/64)
  - Saminsky, Lillian see Saminsky, Lazare
  - Sammet, Inge, 1945 (Box 8/65)
  - Samuel, Marge see Muriel Francis
  - San Francisco (Calif.). Art Commission, 1949-1951 (Box 8/66)
  - San Francisco Chronicle, 1949-1950 (Box 8/67)
  - San Francisco Municipal Chorus see Municipal Chorus of San Francisco
  - Sawyer, A.G., 1953 (Box 8/68)
  - Sawyer, Sylvia, 1953 (Box 8/69)
  - Sax, Segei, 1945 (Box 8/70)
  - Schachet, Gomez, 1934-1935 (Box 8/71)
  - Schaefer, Mrs. James G., 1945 (Box 8/72)
  - Schaffner, Max see Sam Goody
  - Schaller, Helen, 1950 (Box 8/73)
  - Schiff, Bennett see New York Post
  - Schikola, Gustav, 1952 (Box 8/74)
  - Schmitz, Elie Robert, 1943-1945 (Box 8/75)
  - Schnitzer, Germain see Jack Adams and Co.
  - Schoenberg, Arnold, 1945 (Box 8/76, 60/6)
  - Scholz, János, 1944 (Box 8/77)
  - Schroth, Gerhard, 1947 (Box 8/78)
  - Schubart, Mark, 1945-1963 (Box 8/79)
  - Schulhof, Andrew, 1945-1952 (Box 8/80)
  - Schuller, A., 1942 (Box 8/81)
  - Schulz, Carl Theo, 1942 (Box 9/1)
  - Schuman, William, 1949 (Box 9/2)
  - Schuster, Joseph, 1946 (Box 9/3)
  - Schwartz, Rudolph, 1942 (Box 9/4)
  - Schwarzman, Jascha, 1945 (Box 9/5)
  - Schwarzwald, Arnold, 1945 (Box 9/6)
  - Scott, Thomas, 1945 (Box 9/7)
  - Seaman, Julian see United States. Office of War Information
  - Secor, Ethan A., 1942 (Box 9/8)
  - See, A.M. see Rochester Civic Music Association
  - Seiniger, Samuel, 1943 (Box 9/9)
  - Selby, John see National Symphony Orchestra Association (Washington, D.C.)
  - Seltzner, Jennie, 1943 (Box 9/10)
  - Semler, Mrs. Ralph, 1945 (Box 9/11)
  - Sendrey, Albert, 1944 (Box 9/12)
  - Serly, Tibor, 1945 (Box 9/13)
  - Sevitzky, Fabien, 1938-1946 (Box 9/14)
  - Seward, James M. see Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc.
  - Shanet, Howard, 1948 (Box 9/15)
  - Sheffield, James C. see Massachusetts Indemnity Insurance Company
  - Sheinfeld, David, 1945 (Box 9/16)
  - Shoemaker, Sam, 1942 (Box 9/17)
  - Shostakovich, Dmitriĩ Dmitrievich, 1924 see also Soviet Union. Posol’stvo (U.S.), Postcard with photograph of Shostakovich. (Box 9/18)
  - Shuk, Lajos, 1941 (Box 9/19, 60/7)
  - Shumsky, Oscar, 1943 (Box 9/20)
  - Siciliani, Francesco see Maggio musicale fiorentino see Teatro comunale di Firenze see Poleri, David
  - Sidlo, Thomas L. see Cleveland Orchestra
  - Siegfried Weiss Life & General Insurance, 1951 (Box 9/21)
  - Simkhovitch, Mary Kingsbury, 1944 (Box 9/22)
  - Simkhovitch, Mrs. V. G. see Simkhovitch, Mary Kingsbury
  - Simon and Schuster, Inc., 1949 (Box 9/23)
  - Simon, Eric, 1942 (Box 9/24)
  - Simon, Henry William see Simon and Schuster, Inc.
  - Simondi, Paolo see Ricordi Americana
  - Singher, Eta see Singher, Martial
  - Singher, Martial, 1946 (Box 9/25)
  - Singher, Mrs. Martial see Singher, Martial
  - Sink, Charles A. see University of Michigan. University Musical Society
  - Skinner, C. M. see Union Mutual Fire Insurance Company (Montpelier, Vt.)
  - Skolovsky, Zadel, 1945 (Box 9/26)
  - Sloan, M. L. see General Electric Company. Lamp Dept.
  - Slobodokaya, Ada, 1950 (Box 9/27)
  - Slusser, Robert M., 1953 (Box 9/28)
  - Smeterlin, Jan, 1944-1946 (Box 9/29)
  - Smith, Carleton, 1936-1951 (Box 9/30)
  - Smith, David Stanley, 1942 (Box 9/31)
  - Smith, Gertrude see Boosey & Hawkes Inc.
  - Smith, Harry see Harry Smith Recordings
  - Smith, Leonard see Columbia Graphophone Company (U.S.)
  - Smith, Moses see Columbia Records, Inc.
  - Smith, Oscar see Akron Beacon Journal
  - Snowdon, Edward W., 1945 (Box 9/32)
  - Sociedad Musical Daniel, 1949-1950 see also Carvalho, Eleazar de (Box 9/33)
  - Sociedad Musical Daniel, 1951-1953 see also Carvalho, Eleazar de (Box 9/34)
  - Soden, Harold R. see Law offices of Harold R. Soden see North Elba (N.Y.: Town) see Proskauer, Rose, Goetz & Mendelsohn
  - Sokoloff, Nikolai, 1942 (Box 9/35)
  - Solovieff, Miriam, 1945 (Box 9/36)
  - Somalvico, Georgio, 1951 (Box 9/37)
  - Sonnenschein, Robert II, 1949 (Box 9/38)
  - South Bend Symphony Orchestra, 1947 (Box 9/39)
  - Southard, Paul see Columbia Records, Inc.
  - Southern California Symphony Association, 1942-1947 see also Kahgan, Philip A. see also National Concert and Artists Corporation (Box 9/40)
  - Soviet Union Embassy see Soviet Union. Posol’stvo (U.S.)
  - Soviet Union. Posol’stvo (U.S.), 1942-1944 (Box 9/41)
  - Sowulewski, Edward see United Artists Publishing Company
  - Spaeth, Sigmund Gottfried, 1943-1945 (Box 9/42)
  - Spanish State Tourist Department, 1950 (Box 9/43)
  - Specter, Edward see Pittsburgh Symphony Society
  - Speiser, Herbert A., 1944 (Box 9/45)
  - Spelman, Timothy Mather, 1945 (Box 9/46)
  - Spivakovsky, Erika see Spivakovsky, Tossy
  - Spivakovsky, Tossy, 1943-1945 (Box 9/47)
  - St. Anthony’s Polish National Catholic Church see Pulaski Day Memorial Committee
  - Stadium Concerts, Inc., 1942 (Box 9/48)
  - Stanley, Louis, 1953 (Box 9/49)
  - Stark, Mack see Mills Music, Inc.
  - Stauber, Don G., 1947 (Box 9/50)
  - Stegmann, G.F., 1949 (Box 9/51)
  - Steimle, Leonard see Arrowhead Music Camp
  - Stein, Jack see American Federation of Musicians. Local 802
  - Stein, Leon, 1947 (Box 9/52)
  - Stein, Lillian Fuelis, 1943 (Box 9/53)
  - Stein, William L. see Poleri, David
  - Steinberg, William, 1944-1949 (Box 9/54)
  - Steinert, Alexander, 1950 (Box 9/55)
  - Steinway & Sons, 1940-1953 (Box 9/56)
  - Steinway, Ruth see Steinway, Theodore E.
  - Steinway, Theodore E., 1949 (Box 9/57)
  - Stern, Escoe & Stern, 1948-1950 (Box 9/58)
  - Stern, Harold H. see Jaffe & Stern
  - Stern, Margaret, 1949 (Box 9/59)
  - Sternberg, Daniel, 1945 (Box 9/60)
  - Steuerman, Hilda, 1950-1951 see also University of Miami (Box 9/61)
  - Stevenson, Barbara, 1945 (Box 9/62)
  - Stewart, Reginald, 1944 (Box 9/63)
  - Stichting Donemus, 1950-1953 (Box 9/64)
  - Stiedry, Fritz, 1942 (Box 9/65)
  - Still, William Grant, 1940-1948 (Box 9/66)
  - Stock, Frederick A., 1940 see also Maier, Guy (Box 9/67)
  - Stoessel, Albert, 1938 (Box 9/68)
  - Stojowski, Sigismund, 1944 (Box 9/69)
  - Story, Bradford F. see Brundage, Story and Rose
  - Strakacz see Poland. Ambasada (USSR)
  - Strasfogel, Ignace, 1943 (Box 9/70)
  - Strauss, Carolyn, n.d. (Box 9/71)
  - Strauss, Robert N., n.d. (Box 9/72)
  - Sturdy, L. Alice, 1934-1964 (Box 9/73)
  - Suarez, Ada, 1949 (Box 9/74)
  - Suffern, Carlos Aurelio see Teatro Colón (Buenos Aires, Argentina)
  - Sunberg, Harold, 1943-1944 (Box 9/75)
  - Surrey Clinic, 1948 (Box 9/76)
  - Sutro, Ottilie, 1945 (Box 9/77)
  - Sutro, Rose see Sutro, Ottilie
  - Sved, Alexander, 1942 (Box 9/78)
  - Swanson, Carroll see Dadant & Sons
  - Sweeney, John S., Jr., 1949 (Box 9/79)
  - Swift, Charles H., 1935-1949 (Box 10/1)
  - Swift, Claire see Swift, Charles H.
  - Szantho, Enid, 1944-1946 (Box 10/2)
  - Szell, George see Cleveland Orchestra
  - Szigeti, Joseph, 1942 (Box 10/3)
  - Sztark, H. and A., 1959 (Box 10/4)
  - S miscellaneous, 1949-1952 (Box 10/5)
  - Tansman, Alexandre, 1942-1946 (Box 10/6)
  - Taplin, F.C. see F.C. Taplin Company
  - Taubman, Martin H. see Centropa Concert Organisation see Sociedad Musical Daniel
  - Taylor, Alice see Los Angeles Philharmonic Orchestra
  - Taylor, Miss., 1950 (Box 10/7)
  - Taylor, William A. see Musical Courier
  - Teatro alla Scala, 1950 (Box 10/8)
  - Teatro Colón (Buenos Aires, Argentina), 1950-1951 (Box 10/9)
  - Teatro comunale di Firenze, 1951-1953 (Box 10/10)
  - Teatro di San Carlo, 1950-1953 (Box 10/11)
  - Teatro La Fenice, 1953 (Box 10/12)
  - Teatro massimo (Palermo, Italy), 1949 (Box 10/13)
  - Temianka, Henri, 1944-1946 (Box 10/14)
  - Teyte, Maggie, 1946 (Box 10/15)
  - Therrien, Henri, 1945 (Box 10/16)
  - Therrien, Jeanne see Therrien, Henri
  - Thew, Francis, 1948 (Box 10/17)
  - This Week Magazine see Muriel Francis
  - Tho, 1951 (Box 10/18)
  - Thomas, Merrill L. see Merrill L. Thomas Real Estate Insurance
  - Thomson, Virgil, 1944-1947 (Box 10/19)
  - Time, Inc., 1949-1953 (Box 10/20)
  - Toch, Ernst, 1942-1943 (Box 10/21)
  - Todd, n.d. (Box 10/22)
  - Todd, John B., n.d. (Box 10/23)
  - Toldi, Julius, 1949 (Box 10/24)
  - Tollafield, Chas M. see A.I. Root Company
  - Tollefsen, Carl H. see Violin Teachers Guild
  - Tompkins, M. E. see Associated Music Publishers
  - Torke, George, 1942 (Box 10/25)
  - Toscanini, Arturo, 1934-1936 (Box 10/26)
  - Town Hall Club, 1944 (Box 10/27)
  - Trammell, Niles see National Broadcasting Company, Inc.
  - Trencher, Bernard see Albert B. Ashforth, Inc.
  - Tribune Company see Cassidy, Claudia
  - Triggs, Harold, 1942-1945 (Box 10/28)
  - Troytchack, Edith L., 1945-1950 (Box 10/29)
  - Tuck, Jay Nelson see New York Post